Guide to the Stanford University, Capital Planning and Management, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Medical School Facilities Planning Loading Dock (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Medical School Facilities Planning Parking (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Medical School Facilities Planning LR Plan Group (Box 30, Folder 18)
- AMR (Advanced Materials Research Building) 1987 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- AMR RFP (Box 30, Folder 20)
- AMR Concept Approval (Box 30, Folder 21)
- AMR Consultants (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Construction Manager (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Project Team (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Team Kickoff (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Program Phase I and II (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Center for Materials Research (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Revised Concept/Site (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos 1985-1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos Litigation (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos Review Draft 1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos Survey 1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos Study (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos Legislation 1987 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos Notifications (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos in Dorms (Box 31, Folder 14)
- VPPM CCBSP (Cabinet Committee on Budget and Strategic Planning) Report 9/1991 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- VPPM CCBSP Background (Box 31, Folder 16)
- VPPM CCBSP Report 8/1991 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- VPPM Work Analyses (Box 31, Folder 18)
- VPPM Administrative Resources Work Analysis (Box 31, Folder 19)
- VPPM Repositioning 1991 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- VPPM Facilities, Budgets (Box 31, Folder 21)
- VPPM Facilities Department Report 1/1992 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- VPPM Bacchetti Liaison Team (Box 31, Folder 23)
- VPPM Target Advisory Group (Box 31, Folder 24)
- VPPM Liaison Team Communication, Meeting (Box 31, Folder 25)
- VPPM CCBSP Report 1/1992 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- VPPM Presentation Materials (Box 31, Folder 27)
- VPPM CCBSP Target Announcement 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Repositioning and Budget Reduction Program Round 1 Meeting 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Repositioning Steering Committee (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Repositioning Target Setting (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Repositioning Administrative Council/Dean's Council Meeting 1990 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Repositioning Affirmative Action and Downsizing (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Repositioning Agendas (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Repositioning Communication (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Repositioning Data Collection (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Repositioning Downsizing (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Repositioning Executive Committee Meeting (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Repositioning Financial (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Repositioning General (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Repositioning HR (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Repositioning Rosse Correspondence and QandA (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Repositioning Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Repositioning Binder 1-3 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Safety and Code - Asbestos Reports 1985-86 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Safety and Code - Smoke Detector Ordinance (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Safety and Code - Fire Protection (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Safety and Code - Biohazards Policy (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Safety and Code - Fume Hood Compliance Program 1987 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Safety and Code - Underground Tanks Program 1986-88 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Safety and Code - Front End Chemicals (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Safety and Code - Insurance and Risk Management Report 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Safety and Code - Insurance and Risk Management Report 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Safety and Code - Earthquake Risk Management 1981-1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Safety and Code - Program Origin 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Safety and Code - Integrated Pest Management (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Safety and Code - Strategies and Studies 1976-78 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Safety and Code - Health and Safety 1988 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Safety and Code - Health and Safety SRI Recommendation 1988 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- 1050 Arastradero (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Archeological Resources (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Architect Section 1980-1988 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- University Architect (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Anatomy Modulars 1990 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Buck Estate 1979-1990 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Chilled Water 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Escondido Village 1976-1985 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Water 1990-1997 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Facilities - Facilities Development 1985-1991 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Facilities - Facility Projects 1977-1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Facilities - Facility Project Management (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Anatomy Building (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Kimball Hall (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Photogrammetric Mapping 1986 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- General Use Permit 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- GTE DC Power Building 1970-1983 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Guernsey Field 1973-1980 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Hillview Porter Project (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Hanna House Board of Governors (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Hopkins Marine Station 1976-1988 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Hovden Cannery 1976-1988 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Jasper Ridge (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Strategic Planning - Office of Development (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Strategic Planning - Humanities and Sciences (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Strategic Planning - Arboretum Region White Paper 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Strategic Planning - HEPL (High Energy Physics Laboratory) (Box 34, Folder 4)
- NWC Parkinson Proposal (Box 34, Folder 5)
- NWC SEQ (Box 34, Folder 6)
- NWC Hewlett (Box 34, Folder 7)
- NWC Futures Meetings 1986 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- NWC Knoll Meeting (Box 34, Folder 9)
- NWC Fundraising General (Box 34, Folder 10)
- NWC Fundraising Strategy (Box 34, Folder 11)
- NWC Fundraising Fundamental Gifts (Box 34, Folder 12)
- NWC Fundraising Strategy (Box 34, Folder 13)
- NWC Fundraising Donor Advisory Group (Box 34, Folder 14)
- NWC Fundraising Ford Visit 1988 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- NWC Fundraising Bennett Talk (Box 34, Folder 16)
- NWC Fundraising Campaign - Kennedy Resource Group 1986 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- NWC Fundraising (Box 34, Folder 18)
- NWC Fundraising Jonsson (Box 34, Folder 19)
- NWC Futures Meetings 1989 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- NWC Future of Futures (Box 34, Folder 21)
- NWC Futures Meetings 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- NWC Gibbons (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Exedra Building (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Financing (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Sallie Mae Designated Funds (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Equipment in Building Projects (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Exedra Mini Labs (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Information Sciences Building (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Hopkins Marine Station 1980-87 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- United Stanford Workers Agreement 1992 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- University Fellows 1984 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Overseas Studies Reports 1982 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Overseas Studies Oxford Campus Move (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Outdoor Art 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- NWC Cost Study 1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- NWC Bacchetti 1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- NWC Permaflex Building (Box 35, Folder 4)
- NWC Keck Post Occupancy Evaluation 1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- NWC Libraries (Box 35, Folder 6)
- NWC Phase II (Box 35, Folder 7)
- NWC Physics (Box 35, Folder 8)
- NWC Project Implementation and Management (Box 35, Folder 9)
- NWC Remodeling and Interim Use Guidelines 1987 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- NWC Buck Estate Retreat 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- NWC Placement with Deans and Provost (Box 35, Folder 12)
- NWC Roble Gym, Tennis Courts (Box 35, Folder 13)
- NWC Seismic (Box 35, Folder 14)
- NWC Siegman Centennial Overload (Box 35, Folder 15)
- NWC Sequencing (Box 35, Folder 16)
- NWC SMRL (Box 35, Folder 17)
- NWC South Service Road (Box 35, Folder 18)
- NWC Utilities (Box 35, Folder 19)
- NWC Parking (Box 35, Folder 20)
- NWC Planning Group Meetings 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- NWC Agendas 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Planning Staff Agendas (Box 35, Folder 23)
- NWC Simultaneous Starts (Box 35, Folder 24)
- NWC Statistics 1988 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- NWC Overflow/Surge Space (Box 35, Folder 26)
- NWC Phase I 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- NWC Phase I Program Statement 7/1985 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Facilities - 04-490 McCullough 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Facilities - 04-500 Physics (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 04-520 Varian (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 04-540 Durand 1983-1988 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 04-550 Skilling (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 04-560 Mitchell 1982-1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 04-650 Roble Gym (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 04-700 Terman (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 04-950T Hansen Labs (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 05-710 Governor's Corner (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 05 New Student Housing 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 05-010 Lagunita Court (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 05-100 Roble (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Facilities - Quad 90 Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 90- Research Park (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 90-209 Hamilton (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 90- 770 Welch Rd. (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station General (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station Marinostat Building (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station Horden (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 90-130 Hopkins Marine Station Agassiz Lab (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 90-150T Hopkins Marine Station Administration Building (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 90-160 Hopkins Marine Station Cottage (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 90-170T Hopkins Marine Station Offices (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 90- Heuristic Programming Project Welch Road Move (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 90-909 800 Welch Road Rental (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 90-910 201 Hamilton Rental (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 90-918 Addiction Lab 701 Welch (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Facilities - 90-925 Welch Road Medical Development (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Facilities - 90-926 Welch Road Buildings Rental (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Facilities - 90-928 750 Welch Rental (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Facilities - 90-931 951 Welch Medical School (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Facilities - 90-932 Palo Alto Storage Warehouse (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Facilities - 90- 205 Hamilton Rental (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Facilities - 90- Overseas Campuses (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Facilities - 90- Campus Drive Extension (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Facilities - 90- SLAC (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Facilities - 90- Stanford Barn (commercial building) (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Facilities - 90- CSLI (Research Center on Language Information) (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 14-990T Ventura Hall Modulars (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 14-995 Ventura Hall (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 02-500 Terman (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 02-400 Bechtel International Center (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 05 Roble Seismic (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 05-200 Florence Moore (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 05-300 Knoll (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 05-310 Knoll Garage (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 05-350 Boathouses and Lake (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 05-430 Phi Delta Theta (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 05-450 Kappa Sigma (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 05-510 Lake House (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 05-900T/910T Music Modulars (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 05-530 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 05-920T (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 04-240 High Energy Physics Lab (HEPL) (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 04-230 Applied Physics (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 04-250 HEPL (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 04-300 Electricity Research Lab (ERL) (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 04-350 Applied Electronics Lab (AEL) (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 04-400 Geophysics (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 04-450 Petroleum Engineering (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 04-070 Center for Integrated Systems (CIS) (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 04-200 Ginzton (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 04-490 McCullough (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 07-250 Organic Chemistry (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 07-260 Stauffer I (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 07-260/270/290 Stauffer I-III (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 07-330 Medical Center (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 07-300 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 07-305 Boswell Clinics (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 07-306 Grant (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 07-308/309/310 Edwards, etc. (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 07-315 Packard. (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 07-320 Cardiovascular Research (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 07-330 Animal Research Facility (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 07-400 Falconer Lab (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 07-400/410 Herrin Lab (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Facilities - Quad 1 General (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 01-001 Graduate Division (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 01-001 Humanities and Sciences (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 01-001 Undergraduate Studies (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 01-005 Inner Quad (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 01-010 President's Office (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 01-020 Classics (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 01-030 African American Studies (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 01-040 English (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 01-050 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 01-060 Humanities (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 01-070 Religious Studies (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 01-080 Geo- Human Biology (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 01-090 Philosophy (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 01-100 Anthropology, Linguistics (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 01-120 Post Activation 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 01-110 Anthropology (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 01-120 Furnishings (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 01-160 Political Science (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 01-170 Legal Offices (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 01-200 History (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 01-240 German (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 01-250 Asian Studies (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 01-260 Stairs (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 01-310 General (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 01-320 Geology (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 01-360 Environmental Science (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 01-370 Physical Science (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 01-380 Math (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 01-420 Psychology (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 01-460 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 01-500 Memorial Church (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 01-575 Albers Wall (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 02-001 Post Office (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 02-010 Bookstore (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 02-020 Center for Education Research (CERAS) (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 02-050 Crown Quad (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 02-100 Bowman (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 02-120 418 Santa Teresa Black Horse (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 02-200 Music (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 02-210 Braun (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 02-220 White Plaza (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 02-250 Institute for Energy Studies (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 02-300 Tresidder (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 02-300 Tresidder (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 02-350 Faculty Club (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 11-310 Synergy (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 11-320 President's House (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 11-400 Ryan Lab (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Facilities - Quad 12 General (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 12-030 Lathrop Gate House (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 12-070 Student Observatory (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 12-080 Artists' Studios (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 12-120s SSRL at SLAC (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 12-150 DC Power. (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 12-160 Alpine House (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 12-200 Center Advance Study (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 12-262s Trailer (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 12-400 Solar Observatory (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 12-500 Reagan Library [proposed] (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 12-515 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 12-518T KZSU Transmitter (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 12-600 Satellite Lab Animal compound (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 12 - Ryan Lab (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 12-650 SSRL (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 12-700 Jasper Ridge (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 12-900 Antennae Farm (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 12-910 Frenchman's Tower (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 13-012 Angel of Grief (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 13-020 Restrooms (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 13-030 Palm Drive Entrance Gates (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 12-100 Hoover Pavilion (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Facilities - Quad 14 General (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 14 Electioneer Road (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 14 NWC Parking (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 14 Molniya Satellite (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 14-050 Ventura (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 14-070 CSLI (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 14-100 Chilled Water (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 14-105 Cogen (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 14-110 Cedar Hall (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 14-120 Cypress (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 14-130 Spruce (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 14-140 Redwood (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 14-160 Jordan Quad (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 14-170 Pine Hall (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 14-640 Environmental Safety Facility (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 14-640 Environmental Safety Facility (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 14-700 Carnegie Institute (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 14-830 School Barn (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 14-830 Red Barn Kiosk (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 14-830 Red Barn Restoration (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 14-860 Golf Equipment Storage (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 14-880 West Campus Tennis Courts (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 14-905T Dendral Modular (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 14-930T Poplar (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 14-940T Oak (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 14-970T Juniper (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 14-975T Birch (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 14-640 Environmental Safety Facility (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 14-400 Biology Greenhouse (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 14-500 Site 525 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 14-170 Pine Hall 1986 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 14-200 Forsythe Hall (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 14-210 Parking Structure II (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 14-300 512 Governors Avenue (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 14-550 Butler Building (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 14-610 Art Studios, Searsville Warehouse (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 04-010 Sequoia (1983) Survey (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 04-250 HEPL Survey (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 04-300 ERL Survey (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 04-350 AEL Survey (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 07-410 Herrin Hall Survey 1982 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 07-200 Old Chem Survey 1983 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 07-250 Organic Chem Survey 1983 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 07-400 Herrin Lab Survey 1982 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Facilities - Quad Building Lists 1982 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- NWC Campus Plan Project Workbook 1and2 1985 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- NWC Writing 1985 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- NWC Summer Project Alan Michelson paper 1985 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- NWC General 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- NWC Earthquakes 1990 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- NWC BCQ Planning (Box 45, Folder 19)
- NWC Group List and Agendas 1988-90 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- NWC Mailing List (Box 45, Folder 21)
- NWC New Buildings GSF, Usage, Hazardous Materials 1989 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- NWC Planning Staff Agendas 1988-1990 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- NWC Management Group Agendas 1988-1990 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- NWC Futures 1986-1989 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- NWC Bacchetti - The Architect's Collective (TAC) 1988 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- NWC Siting and Sequencing 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- NWC Planning TAC Meetings 1985 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- NWC Surge Space 1984 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- NWC TAC (Box 46, Folder 4)
- NWC Telecommunications (Box 46, Folder 5)
- NWC Utilities 1987 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- NWC Alber's Wall 1986 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- NWC Outdoor Art (Box 46, Folder 8)
- NWC Tasks 1986 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- NWC Distances (Box 46, Folder 10)
- NWC Campus Drive (Box 46, Folder 11)
- NWC CIFE (Center for Integrated Facility Engineering) collaboration (Box 46, Folder 12)
- NWC CIS Annex (Box 46, Folder 13)
- NWC Tad Cody (Box 46, Folder 14)
- NWC Computing (Box 46, Folder 15)
- NWC Communication Networks (Box 46, Folder 16)
- NWC Concept Review (Box 46, Folder 17)
- NWC Debt (Box 46, Folder 18)
- NWC Design Goals (Box 46, Folder 19)
- NWC Development (Box 46, Folder 20)
- NWC Engineering (Box 46, Folder 21)
- NWC AMR Planning (Box 46, Folder 22)
- NWC AMR BOT Meeting 1988 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- NWC AMR Teamwork (Box 46, Folder 24)
- NWC Design (Box 46, Folder 25)
- NWC Applied Physics (Box 46, Folder 26)
- NWC Architect Selection 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- NWC Biology 1987 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- NWC Biotechnology Planning (Box 46, Folder 29)
- NWC Chemistry Planning (Box 46, Folder 30)
- NWC Old Chem Seismic Study (Box 46, Folder 31)
- NWC Utilities 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- NWC Workplan 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- NWC Reengaging TAC 1986 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- NWC Regional Profile 1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- NWC Earth Sciences 1989 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- NWC Campus Drive (Box 47, Folder 5)
- NWC Connective Elements (Box 47, Folder 6)
- NWC Old Chem (Box 47, Folder 7)
- NWC CIS Expansion (Box 47, Folder 8)
- NWC Ginzton (Box 47, Folder 9)
- NWC Biology and Related (Box 47, Folder 10)
- NWC Biotech Processing (Box 47, Folder 11)
- NWC CIFE (Box 47, Folder 12)
- NWC PM Orientation (Box 47, Folder 13)
- NWC Project Kickoff Meetings, Memoranda (Box 47, Folder 14)
- NWC Final Siting 1987 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- NWC Critical Path (Box 47, Folder 16)
- NWC Staffing (Box 47, Folder 17)
- NWC Planning Group 1987 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- NWC Intern (Box 47, Folder 19)
- NWC Health Safety Issues (Box 47, Folder 20)
- NWC Bertoni Reentrainment Study (Box 47, Folder 21)
- NWC Intensified Space Study (Box 47, Folder 22)
- NWC Vibration Study (Box 47, Folder 23)
- NWC Implementation Budget (Box 47, Folder 24)
- NWC Planning Budget (Box 47, Folder 25)
- NWC Financing (Box 47, Folder 26)
- NWC Basement Extension (Box 47, Folder 27)
- NWC Construction Fences (Box 47, Folder 28)
- NWC Classrooms (Box 47, Folder 29)
- NWC Libraries (Box 47, Folder 30)
- NWC Centennial Fundraising (Box 47, Folder 31)
- NWC Science Implementation Fund (Box 47, Folder 32)
- NWC Fundraising 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- NWC Furnishing Standards 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- NWC Equipment Costs 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- NWC Interior Standards (Box 47, Folder 36)
- NWC Full Costs 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- NWC Federal Funding (Box 47, Folder 38)
- NWC Cost of Buildings 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 39)
- NWC Cost Runs Backup (Box 47, Folder 40)
- NWC Academic Program 1984 (Box 47, Folder 41)
- NWC T. Allen Symposium (Box 48, Folder 1)
- NWC Centennial Grove (not executed) 1986 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- NWC BOT liaison (Box 48, Folder 3)
- NWC Building Conditions (Box 48, Folder 4)
- NWC Campus Drive (Box 48, Folder 5)
- NWC Campus Report (Box 48, Folder 6)
- NWC CCAPA Northern Awards 1987 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- NWC Circulation (Box 48, Folder 8)
- NWC Classrooms (Box 48, Folder 9)
- NWC Concept Approval (Box 48, Folder 10)
- NWC County Liaison (Box 48, Folder 11)
- NWC Disneyland Collaboration (Box 48, Folder 12)
- NWC Futures (Box 48, Folder 13)
- NWC Glossary (Box 48, Folder 14)
- NWC Group Processes (Box 48, Folder 15)
- NWC Handicapped Access (Box 48, Folder 16)
- NWC IDCR (Box 48, Folder 17)
- NWC Irvine Presentation (Box 48, Folder 18)
- NWC Libraries (Box 48, Folder 19)
- NWC McCullough Model (Box 48, Folder 20)